# Jason Castro Web developer





Spanish (native)

English C2





Web developer, with almost 1 year of experience acquired in the Full Stack web developer career in Universidad Creativa de Costa Rica, along with a 9-month Bootcamp sponsored by ORACLE. Knowledge in Frontend, and basic Backend. Strong problem-solving skills, a non-stop learner, always seeking to improve, eager to work in teams, discipline to work solo, oriented to deliver the ideal outcome for the company's and the client's best interest, Very communicative and willing to take on new challenges.

# HARD SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS3
- BOOTSTRAP5
- Python
- Java Script
- JAVA
- ORACLE CI
- Angular.js (beginning)
- English ESL EF SET C2

## **EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND**

#### **UNIVERSIDAD CREATIVA**

2021 - 2023

Full stack web developer

### **ORACLE - ALURA LATAM BRASIL**

2022

Bootcamp sponsored by oracle

## UNIVERSIDAD CATOLICA DE COSTA **RICA**

2017-2021

English Teacher Bachelor's degree

### UNIVERSIDAD ESTATAL A **DISTANCIA (UNED)**

2018

Microfinance diploma

# **SOFTSKILLS**

- Confidence
- Empathy
- Teamwork
- Optimistic
- Focused
- Client-oriented

### Knowledge in:

- Git/Github
- Business model Canvas
- Web accessibility
- Responsive layouts
- Regex
- SCRUM methods
- · Agile methods

# **EXPERIENCE**

#### WEB DEVELOPMENT

Looking for an opportunity as a web developer / related.

### NGO FUNDACION UNION Y DESARROLLO

2011 - 2022

In charge of the planning, systems, reports, loans and collections. Involved in increase the portfolio by \$2m USD.

### **TURISM GUIDE**

2009-2010



https://jacabla.github.io/JasonCV/



in <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/jason-castro-blanco/">https://www.linkedin.com/in/jason-castro-blanco/</a>